const flashcards = [
  { question: "Sandra Bullock forces her assistant to marry her in which rom-com?", answer: "The Proposal", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/the-proposal.gif" },
  { question: "Matthew McConaughey tries to dodge a date sabotage plan", answer: "How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/10-days.gif" },
  { question: "A fashion-obsessed teen plays matchmaker at her high school", answer: "Clueless", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/clueless.gif" },
  { question: "Reese Witherspoon plays a Harvard Law student", answer: "Legally Blonde", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/legally-blonde.gif" },
  { question: "Drew Barrymore goes undercover as a student and finds love", answer: "Never Been Kissed", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/never-been-kissed.gif" },
  { question: "Jane has been a bridesmaid 27 times but never a bride", answer: "27 Dresses", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/27-dresses.gif" },
  { question: "“If you're a bird, I'm a bird” comes from which tearjerking rom-com?", answer: "The Notebook", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/the-notebook.gif" },
  { question: "What movie features a 13-year-old waking up in her 30-year-old self’s body?", answer: "13 Going on 30", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/13-30.gif" },
  { question: "A rebellious teen tames a bad boy in this Shakespeare-inspired classic", answer: "10 Things I Hate About You", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/10thingsihate.gif" },
  { question: "A man makes his amnesiac girlfriend fall in love with him every day", answer: "50 First Dates", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/50.gif" },
  { question: "A pair meets during Christmas shopping and lets fate decide their future", answer: "Serendipity", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/serendipity.gif" },
  { question: "Amanda Bynes pretends to be her twin brother to play soccer", answer: "She's the Man", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/shes-the-man.gif" },
  { question: "A fairytale princess ends up in modern-day New York", answer: "Enchanted", gif: "/src/assets/gifs/enchanted.gif" },
];

export default flashcards;